yo yo what's up guys did I remember to
share it on Twitter sometimes I get to
share it on Twitter yeah
no it is broke no it's terrible it's
terrible it brokes coppice i had demo
for you but it broke gotta fix up any
second
whoa Texaco peace stop cheating days I
know it's copy Friday that you know
honestly the real thing that I wanted to
talk about is something I can talk about
which is kind of terrible so much goes
on here I like I just can't talk about a
lot of it it's terrible
I can't talk about this oh yeah I'm
upstairs I'm upstairs I'm sitting in the
upstairs I'm working on grape and
development for you guys let me just
show you what grape pandas are capable
of give it a second you see that so
that's like where your car is gray
pandas make super accurate Maps so this
is also using parts of orb slam look at
the accuracy of this map and what's even
crazier is this map is 3d with a grey
panda and with the camera already in
your yawn we're making maps that are
accurate to 10 centimeters look I can
zoom in here these are trees and then
this is what it looks like
okay let's beam Genki but this is the
map is the mapping from a depth net used
to slab no actually the depth that's not
integrated into here so the way that we
get depth is using a technique called
structure from motion ah but yeah so
this is this is just generated from an e
on route with a gray panda look at the
precision accuracy up now you can say
that okay why don't you just use orb son
the problem with just using warm slam is
you get scale drift from one camera so
what we figured out how to do was
incorporate a GPS so you don't get any
scale drift this is a map of our
neighborhood created with a gray panda
and with the camera you know so our
promise is that we're going to
open-source our HD maps by the end of
the year so mapping companies should be
afraid do you combine data from multiple
passes yeah sort of coming soon oh but
this is where we are right now
that's it finding itself in the map
you're doing a nice app project pretty
cool um but that's one of the things I
wanted to talk about the other thing
that I wanted to talk about was great
handes I've arrived so I know you guys
got the great pandas here in the mail
here's a great pan is sitting in and out
of stock comedy bug or maybe some of you
were sticking these on the windshield
pretty nice right at that VHB but here's
a grape and these guys know all this
stuff is for sale at shop comma dot a
hike or I made it work coming out I
slash out so much goes on that I can't
talk about y'all check out my auger
hoodie pretty nice right
I got team ten hoodie chose my team
penalty I bought team ten hoodie yeah
bought team that honey
yeah what out you can keep secrets not
you can't keep secrets this is the
internet Braille there's no secrets on
the Internet
but tell me tell me tell me what are we
gonna talk about on sculpey Friday yo
the reach outside get from people of
ridiculous and again I even feel too bad
to let you know what should i do I
should post their ridiculous emails on
Twitter and make fun of them guys maybe
I'm maturing maybe I don't do that as
terrible it's really terrible you know I
always give this advice to everybody
don't start a company need to promote
call me out with look I'm kind of over
Logan Paul I still really like the
Maverick joggers like they're really
nice pants
but since Logan Paul came back on
YouTube he's been weak I'm a PewDiePie
fan though yeah what days of super is
bad every day bro yeah props to props to
Greg for that right oh man but she went
down today bro went down oh man
check out our checker boards gonna
calibrate your cameras and calibrate
your cameras with checker boards look at
him we got a mobile checkerboard and we
got a wall checkerboard
oh yeah the problems with some of the
Toyotas apparently they don't have DSU's
and they've integrated the DSU in the
radar you guys you know what like man
there's so much we work on now that like
we just don't talk about and it sucks I
mean it sucks that you have to do this
right like now I understand why startups
are in stealth mode but you know we have
we have some we have some amazing things
happening all compatible with with yawns
with pandas you know with with with all
the comedy I merge so get on there guys
we need you know buy buy stuff man buy
stuff it's good buy stuff go to shop
back home today I tell your friends
which do affiliate marketing for pandas
that's gonna come soon let's do
affiliate marketing
you're gonna be on Skokie Friday there's
nothing incriminating the way but I
locked okay well yeah showing up four
sizes to go peace yeah special modify
door slam um you need help with I didn't
watch that guys talk help with the
Toyotas we can talk about that and what
helped is how many I need we're looking
for react we're looking for
infrastructure looking for just people
who are like like guys no physics like
no things you don't mean no it's not
about our deeds it's just about
um what are the negative impacts of
sharing our MD not that many I don't
know can I build hype you know hype no
we're anti high oh I got I got to keep
that straight um does open pilot work in
Gran Turismo
why shouldn't you start companies bro I
started a company once I don't know I
mean I've never had a kid that might be
that might be worse but I'm just saying
you know you know having kids makes
people less happy than before they had
kids it's real um be looking for
react we're looking for infrastructure
we're looking for social media
coordinator but we're not actually oh
yeah but no but but but honestly guys
know things this is my general rant like
I look around at the world and I'm
always like how does that work like
little things like guys how many you
have any bites on a DVD say I thought
this was common knowledge I thought this
was just like everybody kind of knows
this like just not surprise me
price on the social media coordinator
that's right
let's take a look at our view
y'all high-definition maps of the world
see what you don't see about this it's
like okay you think like oh we just took
works on them right on the videos yeah
you can take course let me run other
videos but this stuff is all accurate to
10 centimeters
thanks to gray panda technology 4.4 GB 4
point 4 GB your closing is four point
seven it's not too bad though what are
the black dots oh the red dots are the
ones that are currently a view of the
camera it's being really slow but the
black dots oh they're just like features
they're like points on the world right
so you can see like like they're trees
and stuff
maybe if we turn that off you even like
zoom in somewhere we have lanes you'll
see the lanes see the lanes don't follow
camera this is called panda Lane it's a
piece of open-source software
yeah you guys see those lanes look at
those lanes I'm so each one of those
points represent a feature in the world
that you can track how precise is Eon
GPS for Panda the you know the grape and
is about ten times more precise than the
eland GPS so yeah get on there get
you're a great pianist and it's really I
mean it's not that it's 10 times more
precise it's like it's like 10 times
less noisy it really comes down to the
fact that there's an antenna and the
antenna is mounted on the on the like
outside I'm not hidden deep inside this
phone
it's like want me to reverse 10
centimeter yeah it's more like 10 meters
first 1 meter GPS isn't very good
those are soccer players I know that
like they're kind of kicked the ball
around not the American footballers man
you asked me like Tom Brady or Peyton
Manning
I might have an opinion maybe um
Manning's retired yo Eli still around I
think how much was gray pan 2 depending
on whether it doesn't care
oh yo you guys want to look at the comma
tree let's go look at the comet
my bathroom um we have a comma tree here
base station D pretty well so we're
gonna release our first stuff it's
actually gonna let you guys use gray
pandas I'm in the next shipper plus
release coming up Monday so here's our
here's our gray panda for our base
station which our base guys hang whoa
look at the comma tree if Caesar light
whoa look at the comma tree you can't
even see it so tall it's so tall smoke
time that's I think yeah sounds like a
plan tonight all right let's do that
oh yeah no it's really tall you can't
even see the top guys I don't know how
to turn the light on on periscope can I
do that oh yeah I think I figured that
I'm a tree is where our GPS antennas are
so they get a really good view of the
sky this is just made out of a four by
four we bought at the hardware store I
actually scratch the roof of the rav4
trying to get that home oh that's the
comma tree you can see it out there um
it's GPS base station for your home
all window here and it connects right up
here to this gray pandas gray panda we
also have a Trimble receiver - Tom are
greater than load and Rita looking is
not lit anymore I am over again I am
over over Logan Paul I like the pants I
might buy more maverick joggers but just
as they're very comfortable
when will the tree be percent yo if we
figured out how to ship you guys a tree
check out the jacuzzi in the combat
house yo yo I don't think anyone's been
in that for months
I'm GU thinking about going up with
balls but then we realize that Logan
Paul already did it - bits going on a
comma this week we shouldn't happen this
week we switched with you Sprint's now
two-week Sprint's figured out how to
ship 4x4 us you know it's not fun today
calling FedEx because my package was
late don't tolerate that tell them
they gotta get the package on time are
you going to refuse the liver all right
this was a good sculpey Friday the map
still here
still there yeah I can show you guys
something - I've been working on we've
been working on moving past orb slam
been working on our own orb stuff so ice
a little more colorful just go in here
so this is this is this
oh is this an age do you want is that
why it's not working I see why this
isn't working
I made the map with a not HD route this
is the new HD camera look at that guy's
but now I'll play back a non HD one
you'll see the difference so that's like
a picture of a full HD one well amazing
that it worked at all okay try to figure
out what isn't working but like now you
see the green thing and it's moving
through the space as this moves through
the space there we go so we have this
tool called unlocker which can replay
any of the routes that's a dongle ID and
that's a route ID there we go see that's
not HD better so we're moving through
the world got all those points up this
distorts empathy that's not even wearing
its Lambo right now it's just running in
like la mode this is doing the law and
flag it won't be like no one just do for
speed but look so you can see you can
see it moving through space right there
whoa look it's moving through space
well it's moving through space so why is
this needed in the first place Oh to get
things really really precise right what
we want to the final system probably
won't have maps the difference in our
version of orb slam is that everything
is actually precise to the real world
so we know where each one of those
points are in ecef coordinates which are
the coordinates that determine a point
anywhere on the earth put that happen
you want to buy this one I just cleaned
this that's what I did last Friday
night's telescope you Friday I cleaned
my keyboard get on nice and clean it
yes let's go here you doing here and
follow the camera look look we're
driving we're driving Bros is there any
point in mapping traffic lights or signs
yeah we're gonna map them all
photogrammetry library this is using
parts of warp slam - and parts of just
Python we wrote and this is actually not
a loop closure so a lot of slam relies
on loop closures so we actually didn't
close a loop just cuz the route didn't
close the loop no so this is done this
is a fusion of the camera the GPS and
the IMU
so what does orb Savina check it out
it's a piece of open-source software
it's pretty cool
oh there we go with driving driving
driving driving all right so it's
basically we're going to show you guys
guys there's so much more stuff that I
can't talk about yet but come AI this
year man this is gonna be our year 2018
2018 yeah it's pretty cool that was
pretty cool a shipper plus auto focus an
HDR is coming next week coming next week
you want to talk about the Toyota
problems the world doesn't change that
much actually
I'm gonna talk about Toyota problems
what are you total problems about the
other radar oh no Bruce you're probably
gonna have to figure out maybe how to
change the firmware on the radar maybe
do lateral only winter HD that's coming
out by the end of the year will have HD
maps are those are soon TM we'll see
we'll see about the HD Maps but they're
gonna be good and they're coming by the
end of the year and mapping companies be
afraid be afraid be afraid you know why
because every time you want to get more
Maps you have to buy a car and drive we
have a network of people all you guys
the cama army out there improve
this could be anybody's Drive there's
nothing special about this drive join us
or die as the theme for 2018 all right
No thank you scope ease for joining it's
been a great scope you Friday I don't
think we're ever doing a scope E Friday
again we'll keep it to Skokie Saturdays
and scope e Sundays later if a major
automaker wanted to acquire you know
he'll know do I want to wake up in the
morning and work at Toyota Navy do I
want to wake up in the morning and work
at Ford
hell no do I want to wake up in the
morning and drive a Subaru no no sorry
sorry Subaru people's like the power
glove those funny whoever posted that
slack all right all right thanks RB bye
bye